tennistonic.com 2013-12-17

# Privacy Policy

**General concept**

The most important thing is that our aim is to help the tennis community to play and enjoy more tennis. We will never ever sell any private info to third party.

We value our members and we want only happines for them!

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This privacy policy relates to use of the Tennis Tonic web site at www.tennistonic.com

This privacy policy covers how Tennis Tonic (hereafter named 'we') will treat personal information that we collect.   
We will not send you any junk emails.

You can decide if you want to receive emails by changing your Notification Settings in the Setting area.

For tennis news you can always unsuscribe by clicking on the link at the bottom of every email.

You can decide also which information you want to show by changing your Privacy Settings: Profile information in the Setting area.

You can also decide which information you want to show in your personal profile.

Children under 16 are not permitted to use the TennisTonic service, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of the site.

**We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personal identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We also provide you with the means to control whether or not your contact information is viewable to other Users through your profile.**

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Tennis Tonic may update this policy at any time for any reason.

If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your TennisTonic account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

For any question our doubt please feel free to ask at the Contact Us link as below.
